Alex Furtuna

3 - 17 North Pole Road, London W10 6QH

T: (+44) 7983 567 963 E: alexcfurtuna@gmail.com



Summary

I have been studying the art of Front End for about few months now. This was a huge career change for me as I have been working in hospitality for nearly seven years now. By far this is the best decision I ever took. I believe my passion for this amazing industry and the speed rate I managed to learn everything I know so far makes me a suitable candidate for your team.

Experience

Bartender, Jikoni Restaurant

Marylebone, London — November 2016 – Present

Bar Manager, The Bingham Hotel

Richmond, London — August 2015 – July 2016

I was managing a team of 5 great individuals. Over the last year we have substantially become a better and a stronger team.

Here I have learned what a budget is and what it takes to be achieved. I have also learned how to maximize the business in order to achieve a budget or even break the revenue record.

Some of my key performance indicators as Bar Manager were to maintain the budgeted beverage GP%, cost of sales and to achieve the budgeted revenue which I have done successfully.

Head Bartender, The Bingham Hotel

Richmond, London — August 2014-July2015

Bartender, Cannizaro House

Wimbledon, London — February 2014-August 2014

Barista, Segafredo Zanetti

Arad, Romania — November 2013-February 2014

Head Bartender, Wings Cocktail Bar

Arad, Romania — February 2013-October 2013

Head Bartender, Republica Cocktail Bar

Arad, Romania — October 2010-January 2013.

Education CareerFoundry, Web Development

London —November 2016-Present

Code School, Plural sight

London —September 2016-October 2016

Aurel Vlaicu University

Arad, Romania — 2013-2016

BSc in Management, Faculty of Economic Sciences.

Elena Ghiba Birta National College

Arad, Romania — 2009-2013

International Baccalaureate Diploma in Mathematics and IT.

Skills

 HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

Photoshop

Great social and communication skills - $\ensuremath{\text{I}}$ have the knowledge of principles and

processes for providing customer and personal services

Creativity - I enjoy researching new cocktail recipes and latest mixology concepts to

apply to our own menu

Problem solving - I can find prompt solutions to customer complaints

Marketing strategy - I promote our bar's menu and events on social media

Good command of Microsoft Office suite

Fluent in English and Romanian

Coe Vintners Diploma – WSET Level 2 in spirits